Guide to the Abu Dhabi Film Festival Collection AD.MC.006
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- 2012 Abu Dhabi Film Festival, 216
  - Narrative Competition, 3238
    - No, 3250 (Disk ADFF 2012-26)
      Director: Pablo Larraín (Chile, USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | No
  - New Horizons, 228
    - Beasts of the Southern Wild, 2011; 3242 (Disk ADFF 2012-18)
      Total Running Time: 01:32:00
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Beasts Of The Southern Wild
    - A Hijacking, 2012; 3259 (Disk ADFF 2012-35)
      Original Format:DCP
      Total Running Time: 01:39:00
      Director: Tobias Lindholm (Denmark)
      Danish, English
      Original Title: Kapringen
      Catalog Record: GetIt | A Hijacking
    - Keep Smiling, 2012; 300 (Disk ADFF 2012-44)
      Total Running Time: 01:31:00
      Director: Rusudan Chkonia (Georgia, France, Luxembourg)
      Georgian
      Original Title: Keep Smiling Anu Gagigimet
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Keep Smiling
    - The Patience Stone, 2012; 229 (Disk ADFF 2012-46)
      Total Running Time: 01:38:00
      Director: Atiq Rahimi (Afghanistan, France, Germany)
      Farsi
      Original Title: Syngue Sabour
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Patience Stone
    - Ruby Sparks, 2012; 3241 (Disk ADFF 2012-17)
      Total Running Time: 01:46:00
      Director: Jonathan Dayton, Valerie Faris (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Ruby Sparks
  - Short Film Competition, 217
    - 9 Vaccines, 2012; 253 (Disk ADFF 2012-9)
      Director: Iair Said (Argentina)
      Original Title: 9 vacunas
      Catalog Record: GetIt | 9 Vaccines
    - 7596 Frames, 2012; 3236 (Disk ADFF 2012-13)
      Director: Martin Georgiev (Bulgaria)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | 7596 Frames
    - Abu Rami, 2012; 332 (Disk ADFF 2012-45)
      Director: Sabah Haider (Lebanon)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Abu Rami
    - Being Sayed Rasoul, 2012; 218 (Disk ADFF 2012-38)
      Director: Ray Haddad (United Arab Emirates)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Being Sayed Rasoul
    - Camels, 2011; 291 (Disk ADFF 2012-51)
      Unknown
      Director: Park Jee-youn (South Korea)
      Korean
      Original Title: Nak-ta-deul
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Camels
    - Copy Left, 2012; 299 (Disk ADFF 2012-52)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Copy Left
    - The Devil, 2012; 286 (Disk ADFF 2012-43)
      Original Title: Devil
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Devil
    - Fishing Without Nets, 2011; 256 (Disk ADFF 2012-49)
      Director: Cutter Hodierne (USA, Kenya)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Fishing Without Nets
    - The Hidden Smile, 2011; 284 (Disk ADFF 2012-8)
      Director: Ventura Durall (Spain)
      Amharic
      Original Title: El somriure amagat
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Hidden Smile
    - Kolona, 2012; 341 (Disk ADFF 2012-50)
      Director: Ujkan Hysaj (Kosovo)
      Albanian, Serbian
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Kolona
    - Lehmbruckstrasse, Friedrichshain, Berlin, 2012; 266
      Director: Fritz Polzer (Germany)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Lehmbruckstrasse, Friedrichshain, Berlin
    - Linear, 2012; 282 (Disk ADFF 2012-39)
      Director: Amir Admoni (Brazil)
      No Dialogue
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Linear
    - Modern No. 2, 2011; 3227 (Disk ADFF 2012-1)
      Director: Mirai Mizue (Japan)
      (None)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Modern No. 2
    - Murk Light, 2012; 326 (Disk ADFF 2012-12)
    - We Will Never Be Alone Again, 2012; 3235 (Disk ADFF 2012-10)
      Director: Yann Gonzalez (France)
      Original Title: Nous Ne Serons Plus Jamais Seuls
      Catalog Record: GetIt | We Will Never Be Alone Again
  - Showcase, 412
    - American Empire: An Act of Collective Madness, 2012; 413 (Disk ADFF 2012-53)
      Total Running Time: 01:36:00
      Director: Patrea Patrick (Canada, USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | American Empire: An Act Of Collective Madness
    - Ai Weiwei: Never Sorry, 2012; 3247 (Disk ADFF 2012-23)
      Director: Alison Klayman (China, USA)
      English, Mandarin
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Ai Weiwei: Never Sorry
    - Clandestine Childhood, 2011; 3256 (Disk ADFF 2012-32)
      Total Running Time: 01:50:00
      Director: Benjamín Ávila (Argentina, Spain, Brazil)
      Original Title:Infancia Clandestina
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Clandestine Childhood
    - The Company You Keep, 2012; 3257 (Disk ADFF 2012-33)
      Total Running Time: 02:05:00
      Director: Robert Redford (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Company You Keep
    - End of Watch, 2012; 3252 (Disk ADFF 2012-28)
      Total Running Time: 01:49:00
      Director: David Ayer (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | End of Watch
    - Flight, 2012; 3243 (Disk ADFF 2012-19)
      Total Running Time: 02:18:00
      Director: Robert Zemeckis (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Flight
    - Great Expectations, 2012; 3251 (Disk ADFF 2012-27)
      Total Running Time: 02:08:00
      Director: Mike Newell (United Kingdom)
      Englisj
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Great Expectations
    - In Another Country, 2012; 3245 (Disk ADFF 2012-21)
      Director:Hong Sang-soo (South Korea)
      English, Korean
      Original Title: Da-Reun Na-Ra-E-Suh
      Catalog Record: GetIt | In Another Country
    - Masquerade, 2012; 3260 (Disk ADFF 2012-36)
      Total Running Time: 02:11:00
      Choo Chang-min (South Korea)
      Original Title:Gwanghae: Wangyidoen Namja
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Masquerade
    - Room 237, 2012; 3261 (Disk ADFF 2012-37)
      Total Running Time 01:42:00
      Director: Rodney Ascher (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Room 237
    - Saving Face, 2012; 3230 (Disk ADFF 2012-2)
      Total Running Time: 00:52:00
      Dirctor: Daniel Junge, Sharmeen Obaid-Chinoy (Pakistan, USA)
      English, Urdu
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Saving Face
    - Sparkle, 2012; 3258 (Disk ADFF 2012-34)
      Total Running Time: 01:56:00
      Director: Salim Akil (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Sparkle
    - Trashed, 2012; 3255 (Disk ADFF 2012-31)
      Total Running Time: 01:37:00
      Director: Candida Brady (United Kingdom)
      Arabic, English, French, Icelandic, Vietnamese
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Trashed
    - A Werewolf Boy, 2012; 3240 (Disk ADFF 2012-16)
      Total Running Time: 02:06:00
      Director: Jo Sung-hee (South Korea)
      Original Title: Neuk-dae-so-nyun
      Catalog Redcord: GetIt | A Werewolf Boy
  - Special Programmes, 3228
    - Arbitrage, 2012; 3246 (Disk ADFF 2012-22)
      Director: Nicholas Jarecki (USA, United Arab Emirates)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Arbitrage
    - Bab El-Oued City, 1994; 3254 (Disk ADFF 2012-30)
      Originak Format: Digital Betacam
      Total Running Time: 01:33:00
      Director: Merzak Allouche (Algeria, France, Switzerland(
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Bab El-Oued City
    - Closed Doors, 1999; 3229 (Disk ADFF 2012-3)
      Director: Atef Hetata (Egypt, France)
      Original Title: Al Abwab Al Moghlaka
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Closed Doors
    - The Gates, 2007; 3234 (Disk ADFF 2012-7)
      Director: Antonio Ferrera, Albert Maysles, David Maysles, Matthew Prinzing (USA)
      English, French
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Gates
    - Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter... and Spring, 2003; 3233 (Disk ADFF 2012-6)
      Total Running Time: 01:41:00
      Director: Kim Ki-duk (South Korea)
      Original Title: Bom yeoreum gaeul gyeoul geurigo bom
      Catalog Record: G etIt | Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter... and Spring
    - Z, 1969; 3231 (Disk ADFF 2012-4)
      Total Running Time: 02:07:00
      Director: Costa Gavras (France, Algeria)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Z
- 2013 Abu Dhabi Film Festival, 237
  - Documentary Competition, 247 (Disk Unknown container 12 for instance of Documentary Competition)
    No Subnote Content
    Scope and Contents
    - Doctor Fabre Will Cure You, 2013; 281 (Disk ADFF 2013-60)
      Total Running Time: 01:01:00
      Director: Pierre Coulibeuf (Belgium, France)
      Dutch, English, French
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Doctor Fabre Will Cure You
    - El Gort, 2013; 248 (Disk ADFF 2013-50)
      Total Running Time: 01:26:00
      Director: Hamza Aouni (Tunisia, United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Jamal al-barrouta
      Catalog Record: GetIt | El Gort
    - InRealLife, 2013; 3284 (Disk ADFF 2013-27)
      Director: Beeban Kidron (United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | InRealLife
    - My Stolen Revolution, 2013; 3268 (Disk ADFF 2013-6)
      Director: Nahid Persson Sarvestani (Sweden)
      Farsi, Swedish
      Catalog Record: GetIt | My Stolen Revolution
    - Sacro GRA, 2013; 304 (Disk ADFF 2013-48)
      Director: Gianfranco Rosi (Italy)
      Italian
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Sacro GRA
    - School of Babel, 2013; 3301 (Disk ADFF 2013-44)
      Director: Julie Bertuccelli (France)
      Original Title: La Cour de Babel
      Catalog Record: GetIt | School Of Babel
    - Whispers of the Cities, 2013; 294 (Disk ADFF 2013-54)
      Total Running Time: 01:02:00
      Director: Kasim Abid (Iraq, United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Hams al-mudan
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Whispers Of The Cities
  - Emirates Film Competition, 240
    - Against the Wind, 2012; 293 (Disk ADFF 2013-57)
      Director: Aisha Abdullah (United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Dhid al reeh
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Against The Wind
    - Bader, 2012; 251 (Disk ADFF 2013-53)
      Director: Sara Al-Saadi, Maaria Assami, Latifa Al-Darwish (Qatar)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Bader
    - Daddy ABC, 2012; 257 (Disk ADFF 2013-69)
      Original Format:HDCAM
      Director: Hamad Alawar (United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Abjadiyat al ubuwa
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Daddy ABC
    - Feeding Five Hundred, 2012; 241 (Disk ADFF 2013-56)
      Director: Rafed Al-Harthi, Ray Haddad (United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Itaa'm khams miya
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Feeding Five Hundred
    - Guilt, 2013; 3297 (Disk ADFF 2013-41)
      Director: Abdulrahman Al Madani (United Arabi Emirates)
      Original Title: Dhanb
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Guilt
    - Happy Birthday Younis, 2013; 260 (Disk ADFF 2013-70)
      Original Title: Eid milad Younis
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Happy Birthday Younis
    - Ice, 2013; 259 (Disk ADFF 2013-71)
      Director: Omar Ibrahim (United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Thalj
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Ice
    - Marionette, 2013; 409 (Disk ADFF 2013-58)
      Director: Sophia Jawad (United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Marionette al duma al mutaharika
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Marionette
    - Men Subdue, 2012; 3283 (Disk ADFF 2013-26)
      Director: Saeed Almas (United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Qahar al rijal
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Men Subdue
    - Mirror, 2013; 324 (Disk ADFF 2013-52)
      Director: Ameera Madhi (United Arab Emirates)
      Original Title: Maraa'
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Mirror
    - My Pink Room, 2013; 342 (Disk ADFF 2013-66)
      Director: Vachan Sharma (Kuwait)
      Original Title: Ghurfati zahriyat al lawn
      Catalog Record: GetIt | My Pink Room
    - Safi, 2012; 331 (Disk ADFF 2013-68)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Safi
    - The Taxi Driver, 2013; 310 (Disk ADFF 2013-55)
      Director: Shaddad Musalmy (Oman)
      Original Title: Saii'q Taxi
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Taxi Driver
    - With Time, 2013; 262 (Disk ADFF 2013-67)
      Director: Malak Quota (United Arab Emirates, Saudi Arabia)
      Original Title: Maa' al zaman
      Catalog Record: GetIt | With Time
  - Narrative Competition, 287
    - Enemy, 2013; 288 (Disk ADFF 2013-59)
      Director: Denis Villeneuve (Canada, Spain)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Enemy
    - An Episode in the Life of an Iron Picker, 2013; 3285 (Disk ADFF 2013-28)
      Total Running Time: 01:14:00
      Director: Danis Tanović (Bosnia and Herzegovina, France, Slovenia)
      Bosnian
      Original Title: Epizoda u zivotu beraca zeljeza
      Catalog Record: GetIt | An Episode In The Life Of An Iron Picker
    - For Those Who Can Tell No Tales, 2013; 329 (Disk ADFF 2013-62)
      Total Running Time: 01:12:00
      Director: Jasmila Žbanić (Bosnia and Herzegovina, Qatar). Language: Bosnian, English. Original Title: Za one koji ne mogu da govore.
    - Ida, 2013; 3279 (Disk ADFF 2013-22)
      Total Running Time: 01:20:00
      Director: Pawel Pawlikowski (Poland, Denmark)
      Polish
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Ida
    - Jealousy, 2013; 3298 (Disk ADFF 2013-42)
      Total Running Time: 01:16:00
      Director: Philippe Garrel (France)
      Original Title: La Jalousie
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Jealousy
    - My Sweet Pepper Land, 2013; 3269 (Disk ADFF 2013-7)
      Director: Hiner Saleem (Iraq, France, Germany, United Arab Emirates)
      Kurdish
      Original Title: Biladi al-halwa...biladi al-hada
      Catalog Record: GetIt | My Sweet Pepper Land
    - Night Moves, 2013; 3293 (Disk ADFF 2013-37)
      Total Running Time: 01:52:00
      Director: Kelly Reichardt (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Night Moves
    - Philomena, 2013; 3286 (Disk ADFF 2013-29)
      Director: Stephen Frears (United Kingdom, USA, France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Philomena
    - A Touch of Sin, 2013; 3280 (Disk ADFF 2013-23)
      Total Running Time: 02:09:00
      Director: Jia Zhangke (China, Japan)
      Cantonese, Mandarin
      Original Title: Tian zhu ding
      Catalog Record: GetIt | A Touch Of Sin
  - New Horizons, 289
    - Bastardo, 2013; 290 (Disk ADFF 2013-63)
      Director: Nejib Belkadhi (Tunisia, France, Qatar)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Bastardo
    - The Double, 2013; 3302 (Disk ADFF 2013-45)
      Director: Richard Ayoade (United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Double
    - Giraffada, 2013; 3267 (Disk ADFF 2013-5)
      Total Running Time: 01:25:00
      Director: Rani Massalha (Palestine, France, Italy, Germany)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Giraffada
    - Short Term 12, 2013; 3277 (Disk ADFF 2013-20)
      Director: Destin Daniel Cretton (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Short Term 12
    - Still Life, 2012; 340 (Disk ADFF 2013-49)
      Director: Uberto Pasolini (Italy, United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Still Life
  - Our World Competition, 279
    - Aatsinki: The Story of Arctic Cowboys, 2013; 408 (Disk ADFF 2013-51)
      Director: Jessica Oreck (USA, Finland)
      Finnish
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Aatsinki: The Story of Arctic Cowboys
    - Amazonia, 2013; 280 (Disk ADFF 2013-14)
      Original Format: DCP 3D
      Total Running Time: 01:23:00
      Director: Thierry Ragobert (Brazil, France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Amazonia
    - Fatal Assistance, 2012; 301 (Disk ADFF 2013-17)
      Total Running Time: 01:40:00
      Director: Raoul Peck (France, Haiti, USA, Belgium)
      Creole, English, French
      Original Title: Assistance mortelle
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Fatal Assistance
    - Harlock: Space Pirate, 2013; 3299 (Disk ADFF 2013-43)
      Total Running Time: 01:55:00
      Director: Shinji Aramaki (Japan)
      Japanese
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Harlock: Space Pirate
  - Short Film Competition, 238
    - Agri and the Mountain, 2013; 410 (Disk ADFF 2013-15)
      Director: Hasan Serin (Turkey)
      Turkish
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Agri And The Mountain
    - The Big Boy, 2013; 264 (Disk ADFF 2013-61)
      Director: Kyu-tae Lee (Korea)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Big Boy
    - The Contagious Apparitions of Dambarey Dendrite, 2013; 406 (Disk ADFF 2013-13)
      Director: Bibhusan Basnet, Pooja Gurung (Nepal)
      Nepali
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Contagious Apparitions Of Dambarey Dendrite
    - Feeding Five Hundred, 2012; 239 (Disk ADFF 2013-56)
    - Mont Blanc, 2012; 333 (Disk ADFF 2013-16)
      Director: Gilles Coulier (Belgium)
      Dutch
      Catalog RecorD: GetIt | Mont Blanc
    - Prettyboy, 2013; 3282 (Disk ADFF 2013-25)
      Director: Sasa Ban (Croatia)
      Croatian
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Prettyboy
    - The Queen, 2013; 292 (Disk ADFF 2013-11)
      Director: Manuel Abramovich (Argentina)
      Original Title: La reina
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Queen
    - Reality 2.0, 2012; 311 (Disk ADFF 2013-12)
      Director: Víctor Orozco Ramírez (Germany, Mexico)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Reality 2.0
    - Though I Know the River is Dry, 2013; 265 (Disk ADFF 2013-65)
      Total Running Time: 00:19:00
      Director: Omar Robert Hamilton, Louis Lewarne (Palestine, Egypt, Qatar)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Though I Know The River Is Dry
    - Whale Valley, 2013; 411 (Disk ADFF 2013-64)
      Director: Gudmundur Arnar Gudmundsson (Denmark)
      Icelandic
      Original Title: Hvalfjord
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Whale Valley
    - Zakaria, 2013; 275 (Disk ADFF 2013-47)
      Total Running Time: 00:27:00
      Director: Leyla Bouzid (France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Zakaria
      M ore Info
  - Showcase, 277
    - Aatsinki: The Story of Arctic Cowboys, 2013; 407 (Disk ADFF 2013-51)
    - Amazonia, 2013; 278 (Disk ADFF 2013-14)
    - The Broken Circle Breakdown, 2013; 3295 (Disk ADFF 2013-39)
      Director: Felix van Groeningen (Belgium)
      Flemish
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Broken Circle Breakdown
    - Camille Claudel 1915, 2013; 3294 (Disk ADFF 2013-38)
      Director: Bruno Dumont (France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Camille Claudel 1915
    - Child's Pose, 2013; 3278 (Disk ADFF 2013-21)
      Director: Călin Peter Netzer (Romania)
      Romanian
      Original Title: Pozitia copilului
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Child's Pose
    - Enough Said, 2013; 3276 (Disk ADFF 2013-19)
      Director: Nicole Holofcener (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Enough Said
    - Harlock: Space Pirate, 2013; 3300 (Disk ADFF 2013-43)
    - Hide Your Smiling Faces, 2013; 3292 (Disk ADFF 2013-35)
      01:21:00
      Director: Daniel Patrick Carbone (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Hide Your Smiling Faces
    - Life of Crime, 2013; 3262 (Disk ADFF 2013-1)
      Total Running Time: 01:34:00
      Director: Daniel Schechter (USA, United Arab Emirates)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Life Of Crime
    - Mademoiselle C, 2013; 3290 (Disk ADFF 2013-33)
      Director: Fabien Constant (France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Mademoiselle C
    - The Missing Picture, 2012; 3296 (Disk ADFF 2013-40)
      Total Running Time: 01:28:00
      Director: Rithy Panh (Cambodia, France)
      Original Title: L'image manquante
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Missing Picture
    - Only Lovers Left Alive, 2013; 3291 (Disk ADFF 2013-34)
      Director: Jim Jarmusch (USA, United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Only Lovers Left Alive
    - Patema Inverted, 2013; 3303 (Disk ADFF 2013-46)
      Director: Yasuhiro Yoshiura (Japan)
      Original Title: Sakasama no Patema
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Patema Inverted
    - Quai d'Orsay (a.k.a. The French Minister), 2013; 3270 (Disk ADFF 2013-8)
      Total Running Time: 01:53:00
      Director: Bertrand Tavernier (France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The French Minister
  - Special Programmes, 3263
    - Dial M for Murder, 1954; 3271 (Disk ADFF 2013-9)
      Director: Alfred Hitchcock (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Dial M For Murder
    - Feeling Good, 1971; 3273 (Disk ADFF 2013-18)
      Director: Pierre Étaix (France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Feeling Good
    - Le Grand Voyage, 2004; 3265 (Disk ADFF 2013-3)
      Director: Ismaël Ferroukhi (Morocco, France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Le Grand Voyage
    - Halfaouine: Boy of the Terraces, 1990; 3272 (Disk ADFF 2013-10)
      Director: Farid Boughedir (Tunisia, France, Italy)
      Original Title: Asfour stag (Halfaouine)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Halfaouine: Boy of the Terraces
    - Happy Anniversary, 1962; 3274 (Disk ADFF 2013-18)
      Director: Pierre Étaix, Jean-Claude Carrière (France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Happy Anniversary
    - In Two Minds, 1973; 3287 (Disk ADFF 2013-30)
      Director: Mani Kaul (India)
      Original Title: Duvidha
      Catalog Record: GetIt | In Two Minds
    - Once Upon a Time in the West, 1968; 3289 (Disk ADFF 2013-32)
      Total Running Time: 02:45:00
      Director: Sergio Leone (Italy, USA)
      Original Title: C'era una volta il West
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Once Upon A Time In The West
    - The Red Shoes, 1948; 3264 (Disk ADFF 2013-2)
      Total Running Time: 02:13:00
      Director: Michael Powell, Emeric Pressburger (United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Red Shoes
    - Rupture, 1961; 3275 (Disk ADFF 2013-18)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Rupture
    - Scorching Winds, 1974; 3288 (Disk ADFF 2013-31)
      Total Running Time: 02:26:00
      Director: M.S. Sathyu (India)
      Original Title: Garm hava
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Scorching Winds
    - Thief of Bagdad, 1940; 3266 (Disk ADFF 2013-4)
      Director: Michael Powell, Tim Whelan, Ludwig Berger (United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Thief Of Bagdad
    - The Umbrellas of Cherbourg, 1964; 3281 (Disk ADFF 2013-24)
      Director: Jacques Demy (France)
      Original Title: Les parapluies de Cherbourg
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Umbrellas of Cherbourg
    - Date Wine (a.k.a. La Sueur Des Palmiers), 1999; 3821 (Disk ADFF 2013-36)
      Director: Radhwan El Kashef (Egypt, Switzerland)
      Original Title: Arak el balah
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Date Wine
- 2014 Abu Dhabi Film Festival, 320
  - Documentary Competition, 3323
    - 20,000 Days on Earth, 2014; 3328 (Disk ADFF 2014-19)
      Director: Jane Pollard, Iain Forsyth (United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | 20,000 Days On Earth
    - Next Goal Wins, 2014; 3342 (Disk ADFF 2014-33)
      Director: Mike Brett, Steve Jamison (United Kingdom)
      English, Samoan
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Next Goal Wins
    - Point and Shoot, 2014; 3324 (Disk ADFF 2014-15)
      Director: Marshall Curry (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Point And Shoot
  - Emirates Film Competition, 321
    - Cholo, 2014; 3335 (Disk ADFF 2014-26)
      Original Format: Blu Ray
      Director: Muzna Al-Musafer (Oman)
      Swahili
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Cholo
    - Don't Leave Me, 2014; 3325 (Disk ADFF 2014-16)
      Director: Khalid Al Mahmood (United Arab Emirates)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Don't Leave Me
    - Girl & It, 2014; 322 (Disk ADFF 2014-40)
      Original Format: HDCAM SR
      Total Running Time: 00:40:00
      Director: Mohammed Fikree (United Arab Emirates)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Girl & It
    - Kings and Queens of Qatar, 2014; 3344 (Disk ADFF 2014-35)
      Director: Shamir Allibhai (Qatar)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | King And Queens Of Qatar
    - Koshk, 2014; 3347 (Disk ADFF 2014-37)
      Director: Abdulla Al Kaabi (United Arab Emirates)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Koshk
    - Nagafa, 2014; 3343 (Disk ADFF 2014-34)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Nagafa
    - Now Showing, 2014; 3304 (Disk ADFF 2014-1)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Now Showing
    - Shadows, 2014; 3348 (Disk ADFF 2014-38)
      Total Running Time: 0012:00
      Director: Mohamed Magdy (United Arab Emirates)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Shadows
  - Narrative Competition, 3309
    - Leviathan, 2014; 3310 (Disk ADFF 2014-4)
      Total Running Time: 02:21:00
      Director: Andrey Zvyagintsev (Russia)
      Russian
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Leviathan
  - New Horizons, 3312
    - The Drop, 2014; 3315 (Disk ADFF 2014-8)
      Total Running Time: 01:47:00
      Director: Michaël Roskam (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Drop
    - Exit, 2014; 3313 (Disk ADFF 2014-6)
      Director: Chienn Hsiang (Taiwan, Hong Kong)
      Mandarin
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Exit
    - Labour of Love, 2014; 3345 (Disk ADFF 2014-36)
      Original Format DCP
      Director: Adityavikram Sengupta (India)
      Bengali
      Original Title: Asha jaoar majhe
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Labor Of Love
    - Whiplash, 2014; 3337 (Disk ADFF 2014-28)